[Music]
smoke
hello everybody welcome back to another
forest wrench video today we're going to
be bringing back something that kind of
started the channel
uh the old 760 pum master classic now
this basically started the channel
it is to this day the most viewed video
on my channel uh it's got like 1 600
views which i thought was pretty crazy
but today we're kind of just going over
this gun give you a couple facts
how to load it because it's actually
really complicated and just uh
show you why it's a great little starter
as an airsoft or bb gun now
as i said before loading this is a bit
complicated there's a couple steps that
you need to follow
so for starters this has a reservoir of
about if it's say if
it says it fits about a thousand bbs but
if you slide
underneath the grip you'll see that
there is
a little hole where bbs can be stored in
the actual plastic
of the bb gun and it's actually very
smart because
you don't have to load an individual one
every time because bbs are very small
now what you can do is you'll take
however many bbs you have and just load
it into the gun
it's very simple at least in that factor
so you close that up
and then you've got a ton of bbs in the
reservoir now
i'll empty this out so what you want to
do when you're loading
is you'll see this little latch so right
now when it's going down that means this
little gate
you can see if you look really closely
this little thing that slides up and
down
the gate is open so what you can do is
you can flip the gun upside down
and kind of shake bbs into the magazine
this is called the magazine
and then you can close that gate up so
the bbs
don't fall out of the magazine and back
into the reservoir
now when the bbs are in the magazine
these are the bbs that you can
fire so what you're going to do is you
want to pull
the bolt back you'll hear two clicks and
then
this is the bb that comes out from the
magazine
and you'll see this actually has a
magnet on it so it's magnetized
to the bb so it moves around with it
which is
really nice so you don't have to like
make sure it doesn't fall out and then
you slide it forward
and then this is engaged this is
technically ready to fire
now on my previous video i had a ton of
people asking questions like
how do you put the scope on uh how do
you load it
how do where's the safety uh how much
does it cost where can you find it
i tried answering those previously but i
want to just go over and discuss it
today to just give you a little like
step-by-step process
now i'll tell you i got this at dick's
dick's sporting goods that's
that's where i got the thing it was like
sixty dollars it's very cheap there's
nothing
the only metal parts on it are actually
this little casing here
and actually no this is plastic the only
metal parts of the barrel
because it needs to compress air this is
plastic this is plastic it's all
plastic it's bare minimum really for
everything now if i walk over here i'll
show you
this is what the scope looks like with
that on the gun it's just a 2x
scope i believe um it has i don't know
if you can see
you probably can't see that it's got a
little plus on it
um and it's real simple actually how you
put it on so what you do
is you see these little rails they've
got little grooves and indentations
so what you can do is you just there's
little teeth on that
and you slide it onto
the gun and then scopes on you can just
tighten these little screws
and then your scope's on now i don't
remember where i had this on here
i think it was like this i had the scope
pretty far back
it's a bit old so i had the scope like
it's kind of hard to uh position
properly but i have the scope around
here
so it's perfect for my eye but that's
just me
now this air gun is a bit different from
most air guns i think because most air
guns you'll have a little canister and
you
put air into the gun but this actually
does not need a canister because
it has a lever like this that you can
pump
up because it's got this tube right here
as you can see
to pump up air into the gun so it
doesn't need any canister
or anything to come with it that does
mean however every single time you're
going to shoot you have to take
30 seconds to pump it up a ton
because the air is not that powerful and
each pump gives it about 50 uh
feet per second of fire let's say um
ton pumps is said to be the maximum
you're not really supposed to go above
that because it's kind of dangerous
for the gun and
it's pretty much it on air pumping so
now we're just gonna shoot it to show
you what it can do
we have uh four different targets
prepped
uh we got two shaked up coke bottles
back there diet coke
it's my favorite and we got two uh
vinegar bombs we'll call them it's just
baking soda and vinegar
we didn't make it very well we don't
know how well they're gonna work let's
just find out
i got my glasses on now this gun is very
quiet you don't need your protection for
it
the gopro might not uh pick that up well
with the camera um
let's just go ahead and shoot one of
these targets and it's quite accurate
now this bb gun is actually pretty cool
because it shoots as i showed you
bbs your traditional size bbs but it
also shoots
these uh this is just this is called the
wad cutter they are
point 177 caliber 4.5 millimeter
little projectiles i'll show you what
they look like they're really tiny
um let's get this open
they're tiny little lead projectiles
like this and
the wad cutter actually is pretty cool
because this is supposed to be
aerodynamic
and keep it not aerodynamic but keep it
in a straight line very accurate shot
they also have little pointed ones if
you want to go like bird hunting or
something like that
uh for hunting as i said and the way you
load these it's a bit more precarious
than before so what you want to do is
you want to make sure there are no bbs
in the magazine so i'll [\h__\h] this back
oh there was a bb in the magazine all
right so you just toss that aside
make sure there's nothing in the chamber
and then you take
the little projectile and you have to
place it
gingerly into the chamber and then just
[\h__\h] it in you have to make sure you
[\h__\h] it back as well or else the gun
won't fire
so it's in the chamber that's how you
load the
opposite uh as you can see the wad
cutters or
the other different types of lead
projectiles into the gun let's hit
another one of these uh baking soda
bombs
smells a bit better
all right up next we're gonna shoot the
coke bottle now this
should explode because it's unopened
shaken up it's been sitting around for
four days here we go
no that's a lot of damage holy crap
[Music]
thank you everybody so much for watching
this started my channel
and we decided to do a little tribute to
it it's been a really good adventure
and i thought we'd just make another one
i hope you enjoyed i hope it was
informational
to anyone but we'll put a card of our
instagram
um because we made instagram and we
would like you to follow it'd be really
nice
subscribing would be nice as well we
just hit 100 subscribers which i thought
was really cool
it's really awesome that you guys
appreciate us that much we'll put a link
to this in the description below again
thank you everybody so much for watching
make sure to like it
[Music]
you